(Howard:)I got something I want
to ask Bernadette,
(Howard:)and I can't think
of a better time
(Howard:)than when I'm
with all my friends.
(Leonard:)Oh, hold on, Howard.
(Leonard:)There's lots of better times.
(Raj:)Leonard, please.
The man is talking.
(Raj:)Let him get it out, and let
the chips fall where they may.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Howard:)Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski...
(Leonard:)Oh, God.
What's happening?
(Howard:)I know things haven't
been perfect with us,
(Howard:)and we've had our problems,
(Howard:)but I just have to tell you,
from the moment I...
(Bernadette:)Howard, let me just
stop you right here.
(Raj:)This is it.
(Greene:)Yes.
(Howard:)Yes, what?
(Bernadette:)Yes, I will marry you.
(Howard:)You will?
You will?
(Bernadette:)I will.
(Bernadette:)I will!
(Howard:)Oh, I love you so much.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I love you, too.
(Leonard:)Congratulations!
(Priya:)Oh, it's so exciting.